Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Course Bulletins MC.286
New York University Archives
- College of Global Public Health (RG 53), October 2016-ongoing
  - College of Global Public Health Environmental Public Health Sciences Concentration, May-July 2017
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for the Environmental Public Health Sciences concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Community and International Health Concentration, May-July 2017
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for community and international health concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Biostatistics Concentration, May-July 2017
    Webpage containing degree requirements, management specialization course sequence, and health policy specialization course sequence for the Biostatistics concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Global Health Concentration, May-July 2017
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for the global health concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Public Health Nutrition Concentration, May-July 2017
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for public health nutrition concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Public Health Policy and Management Concentration, May-July 2017
    Webpage containing degree requirements, management specialization course sequence, and health policy specialization course sequence for the Public Health and Policy Management concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Epidemiology Concentration, May-July 2017
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for epidemiology concentration.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Master of Public Health Concentrations, May 2017-ongoing
    Landing page detailing the concentrations and their specialization checklists for the Master of Global Public Health at the School of Global Public Health. Concentrations include Biostatistics, Community Health Science and Practice, Environmental Public Health Sciences, Epidemiology, Global Health, Public Health Nutrition, Public Health Policy and Management, Social and Behavioral Sciences and Sustainable Development Goals.
  - College of Global Public Health Master of Public Health Courses, May 2017-ongoing
    Website containing information about courses offered for the master's degree in Public Health. It includes concentration degree requirements and class schedules.
  - College of Global Public Health Master of Public Health Course Descriptions, June-July 2017
    Course descriptions for the Master of Public Health. Includes course numbers and semester offered.
  - College of Global Public Health Masters of Arts in Bioethics Courses, June 2017-October 2020
    Course sequences, electives offered in the College of Public Health and other NYU schools electives, and course schedules for the Masters of Bioethics.
  - College of Global Public Health Certificates Programs, June 2017-ongoing
    Landing page for the certificates offered at the College of Global Public Health. Certificate programs include the Advanced Certificate in Public Health, Advanced Certificate in Health and Human Rights, Advanced Certificate in Public Health Nutrition, Applied Global Public Health Certificate, Advanced Certificate in Public Health Disaster Science, Policy and Practice, and Advanced Certificate in Public Health Data Science.
  - College of Global Public Health Sustainable Development Goals Master of Public Health, July 2017-October 2020
    Website for the Sustainable Development Goals concentration for the Master of Public Health program. From 2017-2018, it was considered a separate online master's program. In 2019, it became a concentration. The website contains the core courses, required zero credit courses, concentration courses, electives, and sample course sequences.
  - College of Global Public Health Undergraduate Courses, July 2017-March 2021
    Website containing information about courses offered for the undergraduate degree in Public Health. It includes class schedules, core courses and syllabi, and electives offered.
  - College of Global Public Health PhD in Public Health Courses, November 2017-ongoing
    Degree requirements for pre-requisite courses, program sequences and Epidemiology, Social and Behavioral Sciences, and Public Health Policy Management concentration overviews and courses for the doctorate in Public Health.
  - College of Global Public Health Cross-Continental Master's in Public Health Courses, November 2017-October 2020
    This page lists course offerings for the Masters in Public Health program and links to syllabi for the individual courses, as well as other pages on the School of Public Health site for more information on the program.
  - College of Global Public Health Master of Public Health Course Descriptions, August 2018-June 2021
    Course descriptions for the Master of Public Health program. Includes course numbers and semester offered.
  - College of Global Public Health Sustainable Development Goals Concentration, February 2019-ongoing
    Website for the College of Global Public Health Sustainable Development Goals concentration in the Master of Public Health program. The website contains information on the concentration, skills designated to be acquired in the program, course listings, and sample full-time and part-time course sequence.
  - College of Global Public Health Programs, March 2019-October 2020
    This page features graduate program overviews for New York University's College of Global Public Health, including advanced certificates, master's programs in Public Health and Bioethics, undergraduate programs, and doctoral programs. The page features links to individual program pages where users can find program requirements and course sequences, doctoral student profiles, application information, and information about past student projects.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Master of Science in Biostatistics, March 2019-ongoing
    Degree requirements, course sequences, and requirement checklists for the Master of Science in Biostatistics program at the School of Global Public Health. Also includes a program comparison between the MS in Biostatistics and the MPH with a Biostatistics concentration.
  - Center for Bioethics Undergraduate Courses, October 2019-ongoing
    Center for Bioethics undergraduate course descriptions, including core courses, elective courses, and courses in other schools listings and descriptions.
  - Center for Bioethics Graduate Courses, October 2019-November 2021
    Graduate course descriptions for classes offered at the Center for Bioethics starting in Summer 2019.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Master of Science in Epidemiology, March 2020-ongoing
    Degree requirements, course sequences, and requirement checklists for the Master of Science in Epidemiology program at the School of Global Public Health. Also includes a program comparison between the MS in Epidemiology and the MPH with a Epidemiology concentration.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Fall 2021 Undergraduate Course Listings, June 2020-March 2021
    PDF of course listings at the School of Global Public Health. This PDF is currently unable to playback in Wayback, contact the Web Archivist for access.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Spring 2021 Undergraduate Course Listings, March 2021
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Doctor of Public Health, October 2021-ongoing
    Degree requirements, course sequences, foundational competencies, and program-specific competencies for the Doctor of Public Health program at the School of Global Public Health.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Descriptions and Syllabi, October 2021
    Descriptions and Syllabi for graduate, doctoral, and undergraduate courses at the School of Global Public Health.
  - Center for Bioethics Summer 2022 Graduate Courses, June 2022
    Graduate course descriptions for classes offered at the Center for Bioethics in Summer 2022.
  - Center for Bioethics Fall 2022 Graduate Courses, October-November 2022
    Graduate course descriptions for classes offered at the Center for Bioethics in Fall 2022.
  - School of Global Public Health Graduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The School of Global Public Health bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their masters, certificate, and doctoral programs. It also includes the program requirements and a sample plan of study for each program.
  - School of Global Public Health Undergraduate Bulletin, January 2024-ongoing
    The School of Global Public Health bulletin provides an overview of the policies, accreditation, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of their undergraduate partnerships with other NYU schools. It also includes the program requirements for each minor.
- Non-course catalog publications
  - The Charter and the Statutes Defining the Organization and Government of New York University, 1909 (Box 179)
  - Tercentenary Accouncements 1609-1909 "Three Epochs in Education in New York City", June 1909 (Box 179)
  - The Alumni Electorate Secretary's Report, June 1910 (Box 179)
  - NYU Its Organization and Equipment, June 1911 (Box 179)
  - Address at the Opening of the Academic Year by Elmer Ellsworth Brown, September 1915 (Box 179)
  - The Charter and the Statutes Defining the Organization and Government of New York University, 1915 (Box 179)
  - Extracts from the Rules of the College of Arts and Pure Science and School of Applied Arts, June 1917 (Box 179)
  - Activities in Relation to the War, January 1918 (Box 179)
  - Roll of Honor, July 1918 (Box 179)
  - Announcement of Courses Opening on January First and February First, with Special Reference to the Needs o Soldiers and Sailors Recently Released from Service, December 1918 (Box 179)
  - General Information booklets, 1927-1936 (Box 179)
  - University Bibliography, 1931-1935 (Box 179)
  - A List of Reference Books with Descriptive Notes for Freshmen, 1933, 1935 (Box 179)
  - Bulletin: University Bibliography, 1950 (Box 201)